<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide App</string>

    <string name="restaurants">Food</string>
    <string name="hotels">Nature</string>
    <string name="schools">General</string>
    <string name="malls">Places</string>

    <string name="food_place1">KFC Uganda</string>
    <string name="food_addr1">Acacia Mall, Kampala, Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_kfc">KFC Corporation, based in Louisville, Kentucky, is one of the few brands in America that can boast a rich, decades-long
        history of success and innovation. It all started with one cook who created a soon-to-be world-famous recipe more than 70 years ago, a list of
        secret herbs and spices scratched out on the back of the door to his kitchen. That cook was Colonel Harland Sanders, of course, and now KFC is
        the world’s most popular chicken restaurant chain, specializing in that same Original Recipe® along with Extra Crispy™ chicken, home-style sides
        and buttermilk biscuits. There are over 21,000 KFC outlets in more than 130 countries and territories around the world. And you know what? There’s
        still a cook in a kitchen in every last one of them, freshly preparing delicious, complete family meals at affordable prices.</string>
    <string name="contact">0775987412</string>

    <string name="food_place2">Cafe Java</string>
    <string name="food_addr">Oasis Mall, Kampala, Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_cafejava">

    Each location features a unique ambience with tasteful décor, specially designed for your comfort. To make you feel more at home, we’ve carefully
    selected a unique theme for each location.

    We have over 300 carefully selected, mouthwatering menu items. Whatever your taste, it’s well catered for. We value you. That’s why you’ll always
    e served with excellence by each member of our highly skilled team members.

    Eager to serve you, our experienced wait staff greet you at the door and lead you to the table of your choice in the well thought out seating
    arrangement. The rich aroma of freshly ground coffee is the handiwork of our skilled baristas, adept in latte art. This ensures you get a freshly
    prepared cup of coffee as the beans are roasted on site. To ensure you always enjoy a special dining experience, we constantly improve our
    ignature world-class innovations..</string>


    <string name="place_name1">Kasubi Tomb</string>
    <string name="place_addr1">Kasubi, Kampala, Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_kasubi">This incredible site is nestled on the hillsides outside Kampala City, in Kasubi. This Site was the burial ground for Buganda
        Kings, and four Kings (Kabaka in Luganda) and other members of the royal family were buried in this historical site. The intricate Architectural
        designs depict the ancient designs used in the 13th Century. This site declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 2001 is considered a religious and
        cultural site, but was mysteriously gutted by fire in 2010, but is currently undergoing construction supported by the Japanese Government to restore
        it back.</string>

    <string name="place_name2">Source of the Nile</string>
    <string name="place_addr2">Jinja, Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_nile">River Nile is well known to be the longest river in the world. Its source starts right from Jinja Uganda, some people may be
        wondering how the name Nile come about. It’s a famous Greek word simply meaning valley. The river starts from the Northeastern part of Africa. It
        flows from the surrounding areas close to the equator to the outrageous Safari desert and up to the eastern Mediterranean Sea.</string>

    <string name="nature_name1">Muruchion Falls</string>
    <string name="nature_addr1">Northern Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_murchionfall">Whether you visit by a boat cruise on the Victoria Nile or a safari tour, you don’t want to miss Murchison Falls in northwest
        Uganda. Here, you can witness enormous waters bursting through a narrow gorge before crashing in powerful, roaring cascades.</string>

    <string name="nature_name12">Ssese Islands</string>
    <string name="nature_addr2">Ssese IsIands, Uganda</string>
    <string name="about_ssese">A major tourist attraction in Uganda, the Ssese Islands are a group of about 84 islands dotted along the northwestern shores
        of Lake Victoria. Each island differs in size, shape and exotic flora and fauna.</string>
</resources>
